there.com 2004-02-13

# TERMS OF SERVICE (TOS): PRIVACY POLICY

| |   

**TERMS OF SERVICE (TOS): PRIVACY POLICY**

Protecting our members' privacy is one of our most-important corporate objectives. We want you to know the methods we use to protect member information and the choices you have about its use. 

This Privacy Policy details how There, Inc. ("Company" or "We" or "Our") treats members' personal information collected during their interactions with our products and services. Personal information includes information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. 

**(1) We do not read your private online communications.**

We honor the confidentiality of our members' private communications in private areas and during Call conversations. We do not read or disclose private communications except as required by law, e.g.; to comply with a search warrant, subpoena or court order, to protect the company's rights and property, or in some cases to resolve member disputes. Topical conversation statistics may be collected in aggregate. Of course, what you write or post in public areas (e.g.; message boards) is available to all members. 

**(2) Cookies**

We set and access cookies on your computer for a number of purposes, including to: 

  * Identify you when you Login
  * Provide you with your Avatar content
  * Maintain your session state
  * Present the most appropriate in-world content, messaging, and promotions, based on your skill levels and activity.
  * Analyze and report our total audience size and traffic.
  * Conduct research to improve the overall There experience.

We are also currently using and have contracted with a Omniture, a third party, to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers to administer our web site in order to constantly improve the web site quality. All data collected by Omniture on behalf of There, Inc. is owned and used by us. We reserve the right to publish non-personally identifiable, summary information regarding our visitors and members for promotional purposes and as a representative audience for advertisers. Please note that this is not personal information, only general summaries of the activities of our visitors and members. 

Omniture uses cookies to help track visitor behavior and sets cookies on behalf of Company, which will be listed under the domain 2O7.net. For more information about Omniture's privacy policy go to [www.omniture.com](http://www.omniture.com/). 

**(3) We do not provide member telephone numbers, credit card information or screen names, unless authorized by you to do so.**

When you join There, we ask you for your name, address, telephone number, and billing information, as well as the various screen names you want to use on your account. This account information is available only to There, Inc., including its assigns, successors, affiliates and subsidiaries. 

We do aggregate member information to provide reports and analysis on member demographics. These reports may be shared with outside companies, but no specific individual member information will be revealed. 

We also collect and use other information for internal purposes. For example, we keep records in your account history of your complaints about other members' online behavior, your contact with There Member Services and any reported violations of our Member Agreement that you or someone on your account may have committed. We will sometimes use information about your geographical location to provide localized service. For example, we may use the time zone you are in to make sure you have access to certain time-sensitive features. 

We have two exceptions to these policies: We will release specific information about your account only (a) to comply with valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order, or (b) in special cases such as a physical threat to you or others. 

We provide you with the opportunity to update or correct your contact and billing information that we have on file. Just as you want to make sure that information There, Inc., has about you is accurate, we want to keep only the most up-to-date information about your account. Therefore, whenever you believe that your contact or billing information needs updating, you can email [help@there.com](mailto:help@there.com) with the updated information, or use the "My Profile/Account Info" menu option in the There menu. 

**(4) We may use information about the kinds of products you buy from us to make other promotional offers to you. We do not give out this purchase data to 3rd parties. You may opt-out at any time.**

**Your Purchases From _There_**

We give our members the opportunity to buy There store merchandise, such as virtual objects, using Therebucks and real-world currency. Like other retailers, we record information about such purchases. When you buy from us online, our system automatically gathers purchase data. 

We use this information in two ways: 

1) We review what kinds of products and services appeal most to our members as a group. This statistical information helps us improve our offerings and promotions in the same way that other companies change their catalog based on member preferences. 

2) We use information such as the number of purchases members make and the categories of goods and services they buy to make offers to you that we believe will interest you. In addition, we use other information such as when members joined There, how often they use the service or their type of computer system to make such offers. We also use publicly available consumer data (such as zip-code based demographics) to help us decide which promotional offers to make and which promotions members see. 

By promotions we mean a wide variety of activities and merchandise, all related to your experience as a There member. For example, members interested in a specific activity (such as buggy racing) might receive special offers on new buggies that are not generally available. High-level Fashionistas, for example, might receive special discounts on new fashion lines. Members who choose to interact with virtual versions of real-world products and services might receive offers to buy the real-world good and service at a discount. 

_You may choose not to receive marketing offers from There, Inc. For more information about your choices, please see number 5, below._

We do not give out any information about what you, as an individual, purchase from There, Inc., except to complete your transactions, or to comply with valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order. We share with outside companies only statistical information about what There products or services our members, as a group, buy. 

**(5) We give you choices about how There, Inc., uses your personal information.**

You have choices about how the information you have provided may be used by us to make special offers to you.. 

You may opt out from the There.com mailing list at any time by emailing: [optout@there.com](mailto:optout@there.com) from the email account at which you are receiving There.com emails. 

**(6) We take extra steps to protect the safety and privacy of children.**

Young people need special safeguards and privacy protection. We realize they may not understand all the provisions of our policy or be able to make thoughtful decisions about the choices available to adult members. We urge all parents to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online. We feel obliged to protect personal information obtained from young children. Therefore, no information should be submitted or posted to There, Inc. by children 12 years of age or under. 

We do not collect names, addresses, telephone numbers or other personally identifiable information from children under 18 without disclosing how that information will be used. Teens should obtain permission from their parents before providing any information. 

**(7) We use secure technology, privacy protection controls and restrictions on employee access in order to safeguard your personal information.**

We use state-of-the-art technology to keep your personal information -- including your billing and account information -- as secure as possible. We also have put in place privacy protection control systems designed to ensure that your personal data remain safe and private. 

We strongly encourage our content, commerce and advertising partners to post clearly their own privacy policies and to have privacy control systems in place to protect your personal information. Be sure to review their privacy policies and contact them directly if you have any questions. 

**(8) We will keep you informed, clearly and prominently, about what we do with your personal information, and we will advise you if we change our policy.**

A key part of our commitment to protecting your privacy is explaining to you how we may use your personal information. This privacy policy serves that purpose, and it is accessible through several means within our service. When you register for our service, you are presented with our privacy policy and should familiarize yourself with this and all other There policies at that time. In addition, this policy is easily accessible at [www.There.com](http://www.there.com/). 

Whenever we change our policy, we will give you 15 days' notice of those changes. 

If you'd like to comment on or have questions about our privacy policy, or if you have a concern or policy violation you wish to report, please e-mail [help@there.com](mailto:help@there.com) or write to: 

There Inc. Customer Service  
165 Jefferson Drive  
Menlo Park, CA 94025  
tel: (650) 433-4000   
  
---|---
